You know what? I'm gonna go with worst
song. And I'm sorry I had to do it to
him. He's a legend.
>> Oh no. For real song.
>> Happy by Farel Williams.
>> Is the worst song in the 21st century.
[music]
>> I'm alone.
>> When that song comes on, I I'm in a bad
mood now. [laughter] When you cuz I'm
happy. I'm like, [__] SHUT THE [__]
UP. I HATE that song.
>> It's a kids song. It's on a It's a kids
movie. Like,
>> [__] the kids. Like, [laughter] [__]
>> No. I thought you would be more
supportive. You like Happy?
>> Yeah. Who doesn't like Happy? This is
just a such It's like such a Charles the
Cynic pick. The [__] song that's
supposed to that makes you feel warm.
[laughter] It's related to children and
like purity and happiness is the one
your worst song.
>> Yep. Nah, [laughter] this is actually
Yeah, we are our truestelves on this
draft. All right.